gamesports.net 2019-12-15

# GameSports Network Legal Documents

This privacy policy from Freaks 4U Gaming GmbH, An der Spreeschanze 10, 13599 Berlin, Germany, (hereinafter referred to as "we", "us" or "Freaks 4U Gaming") informs you of the kind, the scope and the purpose, as well as your rights concerning your data collected and processed by us on and in relation to our websites.

We are committed to safeguarding your personal information. Whenever you provide such information, Freaks 4U Gaming is legally obliged to use your information in line with all laws concerning the protection of your personal information.

The following Data Policy provides you with information on how your personal data is being processed at Freaks 4U Gaming GmbH as well as your associated rights.

### Responsible for data processing

Freaks 4U Gaming GmbH  
An der Spreeschanze 10  
13599 Berlin  
Germany  
Phone: +49 30 / 330 96 66 – 0  
E-Mail: info@freaks4u.de  
Represented by Michael Haenisch

**Contact details of the data protection officer**  
Freaks 4U Gaming GmbH  
An der Spreeschanze 10  
13599 Berlin  
E-Mail: datenschutz@freaks4u.de

### Purposes and legal basis for the processing

We process your personal data in consideration of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) as well as the German Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG) and specific regulations (special laws) with relevant provisions related to data protection.

  1. **Contacting**  
For inquiries about our services you may be asked to enter personal data that is mandatory to process your requests (name, address, e-mail address, phone number, used hard- or software, etc.).Before your personal data is sent to us and stored into our database, you will be asked for approval. Further, you are prompted to confirm that you have read this privacy policy in its currently valid version and that you fully accept it.  
All personal data you submitted to us is used solely to process your requests. There is no sharing of this personal data to third parties.

  2. **Competitions and Polls**  
If you wish to take part in any poll, survey or competition run through our websites, we will also use your information for the purposes specified in the poll, survey or competition. We may also save your IP-address and a specific cookie for the duration of the poll, survey or competition to ensure singular participations.

  3. **Newsletter**  
You may subscribe to receive our email newsletters you will need submit your email-address and optional your name. We will provide those newsletter(s) to you free of charge, unless otherwise stated. Our newsletters may contain promotions or advertisements relating to goods or services provided by us or our group companies and associated third parties from time to time. If at any time you wish to unsubscribe from an email newsletter you may do so by following the unsubscribe instructions giving you in every newsletter.

  4. **Community & Game Accounts**  
In order to make use of certain services provided through our community (such as the message boards, chat rooms, forums, etc.) you will need to register an account with us. When you do so, you will provide us with information about yourself and you will be able to select how we use your information for marketing purposes. You can update your marketing preferences at any time by following the instructions to amend your details in the account registration section. We will only use your information in accordance with your instructions and as set out in this privacy policy.

  5. **Login through external user accounts**  
If you have a user account at a third party service that allows you to use this account to login to gamesports.net and you decide to use this service, enter your login credentials of the external service into the form. Services like Facebook, Twitter, Google, etc. offer such a service). The actual login happens on the third party website. From this third party we only receive the following data:
    * User ID
    * E-Mail address
This information is the minimal required information to log you into your gamesports.net account through your external user account.

  6. **Logfiles & Cookies**  
During every visit of websites information about IP address, referring URL, date/time, browser version and operating system is stored in the webservers log files due to technical reasons. Further so called cookies may partially be stored temporary on your local computer. Cookies are small text files that are temporarily stored on your hard drive and contain information about your visit to our websites. This data is needed only due to technical reasons and in no way it will be associated with any individual person. An evaluation is done only in the form of anonymous statistics.

  7. **User analysis**  
We will collect and analyse in which ways you use our services. This can happen by the use of cookies. The analysis helps us to optimise our offered services (e.g. to determine which parts of our services are relevant to which groups of users). Apart from that the collected data might be used for marketing analyses in order to determine what groups of users are using our services. Besides, the collected data might be used to show you better matching and personalised adverts and services on our offered services.

The collected data will only be used for these purposes. We are not transferring any information to any data collectors, list brokers, or similar organisations.

### Categories of recipients of personal data

**Service Contractors**  
Within the scope of compliance of statutory and conventionary duties we partly use external service contractors. We use these contractors for the following services:

  1. **Statistic Data**  
Our websites use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address truncated by the last octet prior to its storage using the "_anonymizeIp()" method) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.  
You can opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics with effect for the future by downloading and installing Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Addon for your current web browser: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>

  2. **Integration of content from external providers**  
In our websites we have integrated browser plug-ins and links of social networks and providers of video content (e.g. Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, etc.). These services are operated by third parties that have their headquarters partially outside the EU or the EEA. This browser plug-ins and links are identified by logos or other notes at our websites. In the context of the use of this content a connection between your computer (browser) and the servers of the provider is established. This will forward the information about your visit to our website together with your IP address to the provider. This information may then be assigned by the provider to your existing account at this provider. Especially true if you are logged in to your account at those services at the time of the usage of the plug-in at our website. For the information on the purpose and scope of data collection and procession by the service providers, as well as your rights in this respect and settings options for protecting your privacy please visit the service provider privacy policy.  
You can prevent the transmission of data. Please refer to the point "protecting your privacy" in this policy.

Details about the different external providers:  
The following links lead you to the Data and Privacy Policies oft he different external providers:

    * Facebook:  
With the FB-Plugin you can like, share and comment our offered services directly on Facebook. With the FB-Player we integrate our own live streams and videos of our Facebook channels or videos of third parties on our websites. Go to the [Data Policy of Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update)

    * Instagram:  
The embed functionality of Instagram allows us to integrate Instagram photos and videos on our websites. Go to the [Data Policy of Instagram](https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388/?ref=hc_fnav)

    * Playbuzz:  
Via Playbuzz we integrate user polls as well as photo and text materials on our websites. Go to the [Privacy Policy of Playbuzz](https://www.playbuzz.com/PrivacyPolicy)

    * Twitch:  
With the Twitch-Player we integrate our on live streams and videos of our Twitch channels or videos of third parties on our websites. Go to the [Privacy Policy of Twitch](https://www.twitch.tv/p/legal/privacy-policy/)

    * Twitter:  
With the Tweet-Plugin you can see Twitter content on our websites and share content on Twitter. Go to the [Privacy Policy of Twitter](https://twitter.com/privacy)

    * YouTube:  
With the YouTube-Player we integrate our own videos of our YouTube channels or videos of third parties on our websites. Go to the [Privacy & Terms of Google](https://policies.google.com/privacy/update?hl=en&gl=en)

  3. **Disclosure to third parties**  
We will only disclose personal, aggregated information to third parties when this is legally allowed or when you agree. If any third party is organizing and/or managing any promotion, competition, survey or poll run through our websites on our behalf, we may disclose your information to that third party to enable them to do so but they will be prohibited from using your information for any other purpose, unless you have given them specific consent. In cooperation with these third parties, we are using Google Tag Manager.

**Additional recipients**  
We can disclose your personal data to additional recipients like authorities due to our regulatory obligation to inform.

### Deletion of data

If your data is no longer necessary for the above-mentioned purposes including settlement, for tax purposes or other legal reasons, it will be deleted.

### Your user rights

If you have any concern about privacy at our website, apply your rights to request a copy of the personal information we hold about you and want to have any inaccuracies corrected or require the deletion of this data, you can contact us at any time.

### Privacy Protection

The following advice might help you to prevent the transfer and storage of data for statistical or technical reasons. Please note that you may not be able to use all features of the services offered on the websites of the GameSports Network.  

  * You can edit or completely prevent the storage of cookies in the settings of your browser
  * You can generally object the usage of cookies used for online marketing purposes in a variety of services, especially in the case of tracking, via the EU website <https://www.youronlinechoices.com/> or the US website <https://www.aboutads.info/choices>
  * The storage of your IP address can be prevented by using an anonymizer (service)
  * The usage of services like Google Analytics, Facebook or Twitter can be prevented through third-party browser add-ons
  * Third-party ads and ad-plugins (e.g. video ads) can also be prevented by using a third -party tool or add-on

### Right of complaint

You have the right to file a complaint with the above mentioned data protection officer or a data protection regulatory authority. The data protection regulatory authority in charge for us is:

Berliner Beauftragte für Datenschutz und Informationsfreiheit  
Friedrichstr. 219  
10969 Berlin

Visitor entrance: Puttkamerstr. 16-18

Tel.: +49 30 13889-0  
Fax: +49 30 2155050  
E-Mail: mailbox@datenschutz-berlin.de

### Data transfer to a third country

We may transfer any personal data we hold to a country outside the EEA, provided that the country to which the personal data is transferred ensures an adequate level of protection for the data subject’s rights and freedoms.  
Personal data we hold may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one or more of our suppliers. Such employees may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of contracts with the data subject, the processing of payment details and the provision of support services.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time so you may wish to check it each time you submit personal information to us.

### Websites of the GameSports Network:

The following websites are currently part of the GameSports Network:  

  * www.1pv.fr
  * www.99damage.de
  * www.baal.live
  * www.gamesports.net
  * www.joindota.com
  * www.summoners-inn.de
  * www.rog-masters.com

_Effective January 2019_

back to document overview
